Next, we'll demonstrate
the smart search mode in action.
This is the simple interface we've created.
Beyond standard keyword searches,
users can switch to another tab
for our 'Smart Search' feature.
Here, users can type their
preferences in natural language.
For instance: "An apartment in Banqiao
with AC and a washing machine,
pet-friendly, around 20 pings."
After hitting search...
...the system quickly parses this input
into database-supported filters
like district (Banqiao), size,
and amenities,
then returns matching results.
Another powerful feature is
similarity search using images.
Let's demonstrate the image mode.
Users can upload a photo
of a room they like...
...for example, this one.
After searching,
the results shown are visually
similar to the uploaded reference image.
Notice they often feature similar elements
like sofas, small tables,
and comparable lighting styles.
This particular listing might not seem
like a perfect match at first glance
from its cover image.
However, listings often
have multiple photos.
Clicking through, we can see
this interior shot is much closer
to our reference!
Thank you for watching our demo!